[{"answer": "You know, I'm not about making myself sexy on the national stage.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "How are you going to make yourself sexy on the national stage?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Oh, I think -- you know, again, I go back to my child story that I analogize on my campaign, \"The Little Engine That Could.\"", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 59, "question": "What do you make of your rivals, Mr. Perry in particular, given he's the latest frontrunner?", "qSentId": 58}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "How do you explain the American public to back a little engine when clearly what the American economy needs is a bloody great steam train?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, Warren Buffett, as you know, pays capital gains taxes.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 92, "question": "How much more tax would you like Warren Buffett to pay?", "qSentId": 91}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 108, "question": "If I'm watching this as ordinary Joe on the street, I'm thinking, well, I would say why isn't Warren Buffett paying income tax and what are you going to do about it to make sure the super rich like him do pay income tax?", "qSentId": 107}, {"answer": "I said stop him.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "Pardon?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "He doesn't collect income tax.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "Why are you laughing?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, you know, a lot has been written about this.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "What do you mean by that?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, that's a decision not for a politician.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 160, "question": "Do you think homosexuality is a sin?", "qSentId": 159}, {"answer": "We have four boys and three girls.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 188, "question": "How many sons do you have?", "qSentId": 187}, {"answer": "I would embrace them, love them and try to help them through what I would see as a very difficult and troubling time in their lives.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 190, "question": "How would you feel if one of your sons turned around one day and said, \"Dad, I'm gay\"?", "qSentId": 189}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "I have to say that your views you espoused on this issue are bordering on bigotry, aren't they?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "Could you tell me?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "I think Michele is a dynamic person -- someone who can certainly get out there and rally the crowd and has taken some pretty strong stances on issues.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "What do you make of her?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, I can't speak for anybody else.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 287, "question": "In other words, is that the dream ticket for the GOP really?", "qSentId": 286}, {"answer": "That was Bob Kerrey who said it as a joke and apologized not only to me, but told the reporter that it was said in jest.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "Your thoughts?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Well, gosh, of course.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "Have you ever had your moments?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "Well, yeah, I admitted back when I was running for the Senate that when I was in college that I smoked pot, and that was something that I did when I was in college.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 312, "question": "Have you ever broken the law, senator?", "qSentId": 311}, {"answer": "I know you're a Catholic, so I'm not in the confessional.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "No other skeletons you want to get of your chest while you're here?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "E LA HOYA: It's odd, because obviously Victor can touch on this in depth.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 349, "question": "In reality, what is it you look for in a guy who you think can become a guy who can beat Floyd Mayweather, one of the great boxers in the world?", "qSentId": 348}, {"answer": "I get that quite a bit.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 376, "question": "Do you get that?", "qSentId": 375}, {"answer": "I just tap them on the shoulder, like hey, dude, my bad.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "What happens?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "I make no eye contact.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "What is the signal that means if you progress with this, there is going to be terrible pain heading your way?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "Let me tell you the story.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 389, "question": "Do you get it, Oscar?", "qSentId": 388}, {"answer": "He walked out four years later.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "Your father did too?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "I actually went out of my way to find both of my parents.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 452, "question": "Once you became famous, did either of your parents make any attempt to contact you?", "qSentId": 451}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 455, "question": "Did he know what had happened to you?", "qSentId": 454}, {"answer": "I went back to Kansas and I asked around everywhere.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "Where did you find him?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "I told him.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "What's your advice when a guy like Victor comes to you and says he wants to do that?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "I actually ended up not even asking him why.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Did he have an answer or not really?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "ORGAN: Let's just turn to the fight for a moment.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "But he couldn't listen to me 100 percent because I'm not his dad, you know?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "I'm not really sure how the balance lies.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 490, "question": "How do you think the balance lies right now?", "qSentId": 489}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "Does fear enter your thinking at all?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "First of all, like you said, he is a great fighter.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "What kind of man is he to fight?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "He's very good.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 523, "question": "How good is this guy?", "qSentId": 522}, {"answer": "He was going to beat me up.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 534, "question": "Did you hit him properly?", "qSentId": 533}, {"answer": "Let me put it this way, if I was at my prime and Victor's at his prime, it will be one hell of a fight.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "If you actually got in the ring, who would win?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "I had to take the upper hand.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Do you wish you'd had a figure like yourself, perhaps, to help you along the way, to navigate that?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "Well, fame can be a trap.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 556, "question": "What have you learned about yourself through that process?", "qSentId": 555}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 565, "question": "Seventeenth of September, you'll have -- presumably your brother and sister will be there, will they?", "qSentId": 564}, {"answer": "I am taking my title home.", "docId": "110831pmt", "aSentId": 573, "question": "If Floyd's watching, what's your message for him?", "qSentId": 572}]